Those who ceaselessly hone
their killing arts are known as "Masters."
After many generations,
they have gained lethal abilities
called "Modified Bloodlines."
This is the story of one such Master,
the Poison Master, Hikaru Gero,
and his attempts to get married.
How is it this late?
Mom!
I told you to wake me up.
Now I'm gonna be late for school.
See you.
What are you talking about?
You don't have school today.
Oh, yeah.
This is a family meal,
one example of human behavior.
Next up, the mixed-gender
friendship exhibit.
In addition to the art of killing,
the Gero family taught me about the lives
of the humans I would start killing
in the near future.
They lived on the other side of one-way mirrors,
unaware of what was happening.
The Human Zoo.
These feeble, ignorant creatures
live at the mercy of fate.
As heir to the Poison Clan,
your duty is to control their fates.
Locked in Latata
Secrets in my veins Latata
I know you want it
And sure, I love it
So I stay behind the mask Latata
Run, run, run back to back Run
Fun, fun, fun unpredictable but fun
At the end of every mind game
Shoot through the darkened night
Poisoned in our bodies still
Laugh at us our reckless souls
TOXIC
For you I will
Rewrite my destiny
Losing it, falling for you
What's tomorrow Kill or Kiss
TOXIC
Tell me what you want
I'll stay right here
Like a spell, I'll be by your side
What you gonna do Kill or Kiss
Kill or Kiss
Remember sitting down to dinner
with family every night at six?
That idea you dismissed as useless?
That's the stuff I want.
Even if it kills me.
Lacking resolve, huh?
If the future head of the famous
Gero family is adopting that stance,
start-ups will eat you alive.
Modified Bloodline++: Hell's Lashes!
My skin accurately simulates
the motion of fluids.
See for yourself!
Kinosaki!
Did I just hit an innocent bystander?
I'll compensate you, naturally.
Assuming any insurance will take you.
Hey! Are you okay?
Why are you doing all this?
Because it's our job.
But you mean more than that to Gero. He...
What is it?
Run. Leave us.
Our top priority is to get you to safety.
Gero and I need a little more time.
Don't worry. We'll be fine.
So how can I help?
I lost my supply of needles
and poisons to that hit.
Crap.
I'm not fast enough to get close to her
through all that flailing.
Master Hikaru, never fight another Master
for less than five billion yen,
and even then,
only if your victory is assured.
A Master must not risk exposing his arts,
called Modified Bloodline Increments.
If someone learns of yours,
you must kill them without fail.
Kill them to preserve the Poison Masters'
legacy, and build upon it.
Shut up!
I've got something for you.
You, uh, what? But why?
The Water Master would've swatted it
out of the air if I'd thrown it.
I wanted to make sure it got to you.
No, I didn't mean that.
I came here to rescue you.
Why didn't you escape-
Your name's Gero, right? And maybe
you want to be my white knight.
Well, too bad. Getting rescued like
some meek little princess isn't my style.
Gero, I want to help you.
You came to get caught? How irrational.
Mr. Gero was doing
all he could to shield you.
You're a shoo-in for this year's
"Not Worth Saving" award!
How does it feel to risk your life
for an idiot and die for nothing?
Kinosaki.
Thanks for setting me up with her...
and not someone else.
I'm glad my first was Himekawa.
Drop that syringe right now.
It's empty?
S-So fast.
I didn't see... Behind me? How'd he...
I can't control the water.
My business suit's-
You really know your stuff.
I'll call you next time
my sink's clogged.
Hang on.
Is my hand on a no-touch zone?
But I didn't mean it like that.
I basically had no choice,
and it's the back of my hand,
so I wasn't thinking of...
Kinosaki.
What should I do?
Those marks...
You're allergic to clean air, right?
You fill your suit with water
so your skin won't come
into direct contact with the air.
I read about it in
the Poison Masters' library.
I mixed a cream to keep the reaction
under control. Use that for a while.
Huh? What for? Is this your idea of pity?
As if. I'm putting you in your place.
I beat you and cured you.
That'll teach you never
to mess with me again.
It wouldn't be "cost-effective," right?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'll never do it again.
Listen.
Your legal exhibits were great.
Just focus on those.
We'll be watching you.
You're soft. Beyond soft.
You're telling him to think about
what he's done, and that's it?
A Master kills and leaves
no loose ends, guaranteed-
he'll get my Thousand Torments toxin.
It may seem wishy-washy to you,
but I wouldn't kill him if he asked me to.
Is that okay by you, Himekawa?
Sure. I'll never let myself
get caught again.
Let me give you a ride.
"What's going on?"
Meet my shark-bud, Chompsky.
"What's a shark-bud?"
A shark who's my bud, duh.
Right, Chompsky?
Welcome home, Mom.
Critics didn't think much of Egg
while he was alive.
He let go of most of his works.
Why are you hiding in the corner?
Why shouldn't I?
My wife passed away due to a traffic
accident just after we had Ageha.
Selling this painting would let us live
carefree in a nice house, but we'd...
...rather keep our family together.
Hey, Gero. Get over here.
Ageha wants to thank you.
I mean, I didn't really-
Save it. Go over there
and bask in the praise.
Humility just comes off as rude.
Mister...
Thank you for rescuing my mom.
Gero, when I heard you were a Master,
I figured you'd be a real piece of work,
but I guess you're an exception.
My thoughts exactly, Gero. I couldn't
find the right time to thank you...
But my brother, Okuto,
got that operation you helped pay for.
He's recovering now,
but he sends me selfies
of how much better he's doing every day.
Can you believe it?
I keep telling him to lie still and rest,
but he won't listen.
Because you put your life
on the line and fought,
that family,
and Himekawa's gang,
and my brother are all smiling now.
Do you see what
wonderful things you've done?
Wait, where are you going?
To the bathroom. To clean it.
Seriously?
Hey, wait. We want to talk
about your reward.
To be honest, all the organs in the world
wouldn't cover what you did for us.
We haven't got money, obviously,
but whatever else you want, just name it.
Where the hell is Kinosaki?
Picking what to wear again?
This was Kinosaki's idea.
Okay, Himekawa. How about the three of us
go out to celebrate when we get back?
(Sorry! I'm on another date right now)
(Anyway, I'm sure you'll do fine)
(Break a leg!)
(I know you can do it!)
What's wrong?
It's going to be just the two of us?
(My First)
Th-This place isn't quite what I was-
Shark!
Sh-Sha-
Sharkity-shark!
Welcome to the Belly of the Beast.
Date Mission, start!
Thanks to Operation White Knight,
Gero saved the kidnapped Himekawa...
and managed to wrangle a date
when she couldn't be more into him.
Now to tell her how he feels
and seal the deal.
He's already onto me.
I guess I can't hide from a Master.
But Gero, remember Rule 1, Subsection 3
of the Kinosaki School of Dating.
If you can't find anything
else to talk about,
compliment something she's wearing.
It shows you're interested, for one thing.
Gero, Himekawa's covered in stuff
you can compliment her on.
Pretty earrings. A lovely necklace.
Cute nails. A stylish jacket.
Th-That necklace...
Go for it!
It looks awfully old. Is it a keepsake?
Huh?
Himekawa's speechless, too.
Oh, this?
It came with a dehumidifier
I got at a flea market.
Who could've seen that coming?!
C'mon, make conversation!
A flea market dehumidifier
that came with a necklace?
There's tons of follow-ups to that!
Did you, uh, cut your bangs?
Nope.
Don't give up!
Don't look at me! Look at Himekawa!
Hey, Gero.
Uh-oh. All that goodwill we earned
has gone right down the drain.
If you're not eating that, gimme it.
Thanks.
Safe! Thank goodness
Himekawa's so easygoing.
I love these.
L-Love?!
And you're out!
This is a disaster.
I've got no choice but to...
lend a hand!
That must be a Greenland shark.
Wow, you know so much!
O-Oh, that's the "support shark"
that went away due to bad user reviews.
Wow, you know so much!
And it makes whale puns!
E-Excuse me.
Th-That monitor isn't for diners...
Please? Just a little?
What's up? You've barely
touched your food.
Oh, well...
I, uh, can't eat anything someone else
has made. It's become second nature.
As far back as I can remember,
I've done nothing but
train as a Poison Master.
I made my own meals, and all that mattered
was that they weren't poisoned.
I'd just eat alone in between my training.
Excuse me, miss? Uh, manager?!
I'm in love.
I think I kind of get it.
I was alone all the time
when I was a kid, too.
(You'd bet-orca
listen to her)
I didn't have any family to start with,
and I had no friends at the orphanage.
One day, a rich guy nearing
the end of his life adopted me.
I think he would have
been happy with anyone.
He just realized he'd left no legacy
at the end of his life and got scared.
I inherited the Himekawa name
and a huge fortune.
Normally, I wouldn't have had
to work a day in my life.
But...
He had a crapton
of crying works of art locked away.
I did some digging, and found out
he'd gotten them illegitimately.
I know how hard it is to be alone,
so I decided to send them all home.
By the time the gallery was empty,
expenses had eaten through
the Himekawa fortune.
So now, I work part-time
five days a week to survive.
Kind of ridiculous, isn't it?
Whoa.
Earlier, for the first time, I got to do
something people would thank me for.
I couldn't have done it without you.
And you've been doing that all along?
I've never met anyone as cool as you.
Sorry. Was it something I said?
No, nothing like that.
No one's sung my praises like that before.
It's kind of embarrassing.
(Go for it!)
Gulp.
Shark!
Sh-Sharkity, uh...
Himekawa, would you do something for me?
Please...
Be my friend.
Shark!
Uh, Gero? That's was your big chance!
You had me going there.
Friends? Sure thing. I thought
you were going to ask me out.
Honestly, I'd like to.
But I don't know
the first thing about you.
More than that...
I don't think you know me at all, either.
Maybe I made a good impression earlier,
but that's just my polished surface.
Truth is, there are parts of me so foul
I don't want to face them.
I want to experience more things together,
and get you to know all of me,
a little at a time.
Then, if I can convince you
to see me that way, too,
I'd like to make that proposal.
That's...
the first step toward
the happy marriage I'm looking for.
I get it. So you want
to start off as friends?
How should I put this?
That's shameless as all hell.
Uh, I mean...
Fine by me.
But stealing my heart won't be easy.
Anyway, I figured you were with Kinosaki.
Kinosaki is my marriage advisor.
Oh, is that all?
(Friends)
Ms. Himekawa!
Since you can't eat food
other people make,
how about you make us
lunches next time?
S-Sure.
I'm big on rolled omelets.
Gero.
You've got a bodyguard gig next.
The only daughter of a big-time CEO.
But that'd be cheating!
How scummy can you get?
It's not cheating. You just made friends.
And Himekawa is about
the only woman you know, right?
But there's a whole sea of other fish
out there. A bunch you'd never think of.
Getting to know a lot of girls will help
you see their good points clearly,
and you'll learn to like them even more.
Maybe Himekawa really
is the one for you,
or maybe it's someone
you haven't even met yet.
Whoever she is, I want you to have
the best possible marriage.
Ah! Something smells fishy!
I'm shocked, startled,
it's adding insult to injury
I'm completely obsessed
Ah! Something smells off!
You're all bluff,
I'm sick and tired, so disappointed
Bye-bye, mwah!
It seems like I'm only good at
workbooks for a child
Even through infectious disease,
I want to love with you
No! No! Love's in gridlock!
Forever and ever, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Darling, heading toward a twisted signpost
Heart fluttering, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Just the two of us, consolation prize
Ah, the scent of dance
I'm completely obsessed
with you as you flutter down
Ah, something smells off
I'm blown away by you
Bye-bye, mwah!
It seems like I'm only good at
workbooks for a child
I want us to share even our growing pains
No! No! Love's in gridlock!
Forever and ever, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Darling, heading toward
a stagnant signpost
Heart fluttering, I love you,
Shake Na Baby
Singing a grand chorus cheekily
- So this is a college welcome party?
- I want to improve myself.
- I've heard the legends.
- The melody of this forest.
Pom-po-pun.
I super thank my lucky stars.
Next time: "The Sound Master."